[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what year was fictional character Michael Myers born?", "correct_answer": "1957", "incorrect_answers": ["1956", "1954", "1961"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Chihuahua Gidget is famous for what reason?", "correct_answer": "It was a mascot for Taco Bell.", "incorrect_answers": ["Paris Hilton has it as a pet.", "It was a fill-in mascot for the Georgia Bulldogs.", "It was a mascot for Taco John."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What movie portrays Oskar, a businessman looking to hire Jews during World War II?", "correct_answer": "Schindlers List", "incorrect_answers": ["Crimes and Misdemeanors", "The Great Dictator", "Driving Miss Daisy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Alan Arkin, who portrays Grandpa in Little Miss Sunshine, was a founding member of this famous comedy group.", "correct_answer": "Second City", "incorrect_answers": ["Alphabet City", "The Improv Players", "The Daisy Players"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What interesting resting posture does the Indian Treeshrew, a.k.a. Madras Treeshrew, have?", "correct_answer": "With its tail resting on its head", "incorrect_answers": ["Sprawling on the ground as if its dead", "Cuddling its rear legs", "Hanging upside down from a branch"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Virginia General Assembly was founded in Jamestown in what year?", "correct_answer": "1619", "incorrect_answers": ["1774", "1719", "1819"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If the nurse approaches the doctor and says, Doctor, theres a code in the lobby, what is the doctor likely to do?", "correct_answer": "Tell the nurse to call 911", "incorrect_answers": ["Say thank you and resume what he was doing", "Go home because the office is closed for the day", "Pull out his wallet"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who wrote the screenplay of The Longest Day?", "correct_answer": "Cornelius Ryan", "incorrect_answers": ["Jack Seddon", "David  Purcell", "Romain Gary"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is methyphobia?", "correct_answer": "A fear of alcohol", "incorrect_answers": ["A fear of explosions", "A fear of gases", "A fear of pleasure"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What year did the United States boycott the International Olympic Games?", "correct_answer": "1980", "incorrect_answers": ["1972", "1976", "1984"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This 1988 film won the Oscar for Best Picture at the 61st Academy Awards in 1989.", "correct_answer": "Rain Man", "incorrect_answers": ["The Accidental Tourist", "Dangerous Liaisons", "Working Girl"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This annual plant, also called brinjal, is native to southern India and Sri Lanka.", "correct_answer": "Eggplant", "incorrect_answers": ["Tomato", "Cucumber", "Yam"]}]